#### Contact

skbell07@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shameyaceasar-msn-rn-cphq-hacpa14b0285 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Patient Safety
Healthcare Management
Quality Improvement

# Shameya Ceasar MSN,RN,CPHQ,HACP

Director of Hospital Quality, and Patient Safety Houston, Texas Area

## Summary

Experienced Quality and Safety Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in leadership,performance improvement methodologies, patient safety strategies, root cause analysis and corrective action planning. Also skilled in regulatory readiness and accreditation activities.

#### Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System 4 years 1 month

Director of Hospital Quality and Patient Safety February 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Southeast and Pearland

Manager Quality, Patient Safety, and Infection Prevention May 2016 - February 2019 (2 years 10 months) Pearland, TX

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center Regulatory and Patient Safety Project Manager July 2015 - April 2016 (10 months)

St. Luke's | Houston, Texas 5 years 5 months

Assistant Nurse Manager Performance Improvement Transplant Programs

June 2013 - July 2015 (2 years 2 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Renal transplant coordinator July 2011 - June 2013 (2 years)

Transplant ICU RN

March 2010 - July 2011 (1 year 5 months)

## Education

The University of Texas at Arlington MSN, Nursing administration · (2012 - 2015)

University of Arkansas at Fayetteville Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing Science

Page 2 of 2